[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Master.
You wanted to see me?
You used human lives to set the trap.
You're a fast learner.
Thanks to you,
Zhang Yinhua, every three to five years,
comes to perform a ritual.
It can bring a lot of gold to the sect.
I taught you to hunt wild Paozi,
not the souls of young ladies.
Is the killing really that important?
Didn't you ask me
to kill Li Yingjuan?
I killed her to save thousands of lives in the sect.
Now you kill people
to feed your greed.
You're exaggerating.
I'm just following your teachings.
After all, I'm not the only one who needs to be fed.
Didn't you teach me this?
Sometimes dead people are more useful than the living.
The century-old foundation of Tianxiang Sect
isn't built on killing,
but on rules that terrify the wicked
and are respected by the good.
Rules?
Ask the brothers out there who have taken a bullet.
Do they like the loyalty Second Master speak of
or the clinking of silver dollars?
The brothers in the sect are wild horses.
You're the one holding the reins!
You have to teach them benevolence, righteousness, and ethics.
You can't let them tread further into danger.
That's what you should do!
In times of peace,
we might not need to kill.
But look at the world out there now.
We can't fool those in high power.
Those with guns
can take our lives at any time.
What do you expect us to live on?
We can only rely on people like Zhang Yinhua.
Do you know
why Tianxiang Sect exists?
To uphold justice?
It was to overthrow the Qing and restore the Ming.
But
the Qing Dynasty has fallen.
The Tianxiang Sect
should no longer exist either.
We should have disbanded long ago.
We've been with you for so long
and done so much for you.
And you're just going to disband us just like that?
What do you want to do, then?
That'll depend on whether the brothers accept it.
Master.
It's time to make room for the new world.
All right.
I'll
do a final reading
for you today.
Kan and Li are in opposition,
an ominous star offends the Dipper.
Today,
the brothers who risk their lives for you
will one day be
the evil spirits that take your life.
Second,
in your life,
the Solitary Phoenix star stirs.
Your lover
will eventually become the arrow that pierces your heart.
You will never enjoy the bliss of family.
Third,
you can't hide your thoughts.
It's time to go.
You never know
when to pull in the net.
-Welcome, Sect Master! -Welcome, Sect Master!
[A Prophet]
[Episode 24]
It's time.
Execute!
-Kill! -Kill!
Fourth Brother,
please do me one last favor.
Find Silly Liang.
He'll take you to Jialing Hotel.
Director Feng!
Go find Feng Siyuan.
Stop making a scene.
Director Feng!
Tell him
the strong wind is about to rise.
Director Feng!
The strong wind is about to rise.
I didn't expect you to grace us with your presence.
Are you Director Wang?
Who the hell are you?
Take him down.
Wait.
Is there some kind of misunderstanding?
This is why I say Sect Master is my lucky star.
You asked me to go east,
but I went west.
I just took the seat as Deputy Director of the Field Headquarters.
Then I must congratulate you.
Right in your territory,
we caught a wanted criminal.
Director Feng,
welcome.
Forgive me for not coming out to welcome you.
It's confirmed that
Wang Zhicheng, Chief of Yucheng Police Station,
has committed 3 felonies.
The evidence is conclusive.
He is to be lawfully arrested,
by the Yucheng Field Headquarters.
Approved by Director Feng.
Director Feng.
We both serve the Party and the State.
You can't just listen to others' instigations!
Take him away!
Director Feng.
Director Feng!
Please let me explain, Director Feng.
Sect Master!
Sect Master, save me! Sect Master!
The third wife of Wang Zhicheng
is my man.
She has already
recorded down everything
about Wang Zhicheng bribery.
These are the details and photos of his bribery.
Giving Wang Zhicheng's political achievements to Feng Siyuan
is just our first move.
He just arrived in Yucheng
and is anxious to gain a foothold.
The one he wants to curry favor with the most right now
must be Chairman Liu.
Chairman Liu was a military man in his early years.
He pacified the various warlords.
Once the territory he conquered was stable,
he changed into the chairman's gown.
Rice wine,
well salt,
and opium—
all these lucrative trades must go through the chairman's hands.
Even if God wants to rain,
he'd have to wire the provincial office
to ask for his permission.
Chairman Liu is high and mighty.
but only Sect Master...
knows what he's truly thinking.
Next,
we're going to feed this ambitious Feng Siyuan
a completely fabricated story.
From now on,
this book will be called the Yin Book.
We need to make Feng Siyuan believe
that this is Sect Master's secret weapon.
As long as he possesses the Yin Book,
Feng Siyuan will have
glory and wealth in Yucheng.
So now we need to lead Feng Siyuan by the nose
and make him seek out Sect Master on his own.
The calligraphy you and your mentor
got your hands on a few days ago
is the best stepping stone.
Director Feng.
This is
Master Zheng's calligraphy that Chairman Liu has always wanted.
I heard that he's going to hold
a birthday banquet soon.
This gift
is perfect.
What a brilliant contrast of ink,
with slender branches and thick leaves.
For such a grand gift,
I should thank Miss Jiang.
I'm just glad it helps.
But Chairman Liu never sees new officials.
No matter how good the gift is,
it's useless if it can't be delivered.
There's someone who can help you.
Sect Master.
Are you kidding me?
The head of a bunch of swindlers—
what right does he have to approach Chairman Liu?
The Yin Book.
The Yin Book?
During the Ming Dynasty,
the Imperial Guards wrote the Yang Book for His Majesty.
It recorded all the
shady deeds of the dynasty's officials.
Sect Master followed suit
and spread spies around the high officials and nobles.
and compiled his own Yin Book.
The Sect Master used the Yin Book
to help Chairman Liu clear the way
and keep everyone in check.
That's why Chairman Liu trusts him so deeply.
Why should I trust you?
Director Feng,
even if you don't trust him,
you should trust me.
Sect Master put me next to you,
yet I
never set a trap against you.
This is Wang Zhicheng's secret file from the Yin Book.
Whether it's true or false,
you'll know once you test it out.
If this Yin Book
is really as important as you both say,
why don't you keep it for yourselves?
Something like the Yin Book
can only become a ladder to the sky
in the hands of the right person.
But in the hands of nobodies like us,
it will only bring more trouble.
I can't accept a reward without merit.
You prepared such a big gift for me.
I'm curious—
what do you want from me?
What I want
is for you to help me eradicate the entire Tianxiang Sect.
In this way,
you can replace him
and become Chairman Liu's right-hand man.
If you run into trouble,
look for me here.
Jialing Hotel?
The strong wind is about to rise.
Now that official business is done,
I have a personal matter
to trouble Sect Master with.
You're too polite.
Let's talk in private.
This way.
Please.
In public,
Wang Zhicheng is down.
In private,
should we
corporate more?
Don't mention cooperation.
It's my honor
to be able to help you.
There is no time like the present.
I happen to have a small matter right now
that I need Sect Master's help with.
Go ahead.
I prepared a birthday gift for Chairman Liu.
It's a piece of Master Zheng's calligraphy.
You know I'm a rough person.
I don't understand the tastes of scholars and elites.
So I'd like to invite you
to attend the birthday banquet with me
and put in a good word for me in front of him.
And while we're at it, help me elevate
the value of Master Zheng's work.
My goodness, such a grand occasion.
I'm just a person of the underworld— not worthy of being there.
Someone from the underworld saying they're not worthy
is like a soldier saying
they're scared of blood.
So I advise you
not to decline.
Alright.
Since you've put it that way,
I'll...
I'll go.
Great.
Also,
those two people are still useful to me.
Sect Master, could you
make an exception?
You're really making this difficult for me.
But since you've asked,
I must give you some face.
How about this?
I'll let one of them go.
Who will you choose?
Miss Jiang.
You may leave now.
Only one of those two?
But I have use for both of them.
Releasing only one makes it hard for me.
You're the one making it hard for me.
I've promised you to let one go.
Besides,
I have to take you to Chairman Liu.
I've given you
enough respect and kindness.
Shouldn't you
do the same for me?
That makes sense.
How about an exchange of hostages?
Who carries that much weight?
Zhang Dancheng.
Mentor.
Why are you back?
How could I not come for such a big matter?
You shouldn't have come back.
Sect Master is in the room.
I've talked to Feng Siyuan.
He will take me away.
Get out of here.
Since I dare to come,
I have a plan.
You taught me.
I know exactly what you're thinking.
When I'm gone,
you must remember
how your path forward
should be walked.
Zhang Dancheng.
After I kill the Sect Master,
I'll come back for your life.
Kid,
I'm returning my life
to you.
What a rare guest.
It's truly been a while since you've been back.
Something's up?
Something's up.
What is it?
A life exchange.
Tired of living?
Have been for a long time.
Deal.
How do you want to die?
I have a choice?
Yes.
How about I set up a table of food and wine?
I'll have a drink.
And you have a little too.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll hold a grand funeral for you.
I promise you'll go out in style.
Too much trouble.
Not at all.
It's worth it for you.
Just like what I said
when I asked Old Sect Master to save you—
you are a talent.
You flatter me.
I'm not that capable.
If I were,
I wouldn't have let Old Sect Master
die in your hands.
You still remember this?
Old Sect Master wanted to disband Tianxiang Sect.
Where would our hundreds of brothers go?
What would be their livelihood?
I had no choice.
Every generation brings forth new talents,
so I took this position
and became the new Sect Master.
Does Shangguan Hong think so too?
I really don't know.
I've been thinking about this for many years—
and still haven't figured it out.
Why don't you tell me?
I was blind back then.
I shouldn't have brought her back.
[Eight years ago]
Senior.
When did the child pass away?
He died of illness.
It hasn't even been half a year.
How did you find this place?
Shangguan Chengming...
He took your surname?
Yes.
I don't want him to know
anything about his father.
His father is already the Sect Master.
I thought he died long ago.
He got there
by killing the Old Sect Master, Shen Yunhe,
to take that position.
With him, Tianxiang Sect has changed.
The entire sect is an absolute mess.
What does it have to do with me?
I want to take you back.
You want to use me
to threaten him?
WIth you around,
I can guarantee he steps down
without spilling any blood.
This is the best way I can think of.
In the entire Tianxiang Sect,
you're the only one who still believes in sentiment.
Now that he's the Sect Master,
how could he, for an old lover,
give up his empire?
As long as you can't bring yourself to kill me...
I've made up my mind.
I'll take you back.
You used Shangguan Hong to force me to abdicate
and brought a little swindler to pretend to be my son.
But what you didn't expect is that
my relationship with Shangguan Hong was over.
That little swindler—
you didn't teach him well.
You taught him to be too kind.
I know you already knew
he would come back to save me,
which is why you agreed to let him go.
On the road to the underworld,
I'll find you a companion.
You're so cruel.
Not as evil as you.
You're too polite.
You flatter me.
Let me tell you something.
You've actually seen the real Shangguan Chengming.
From now on,
you are my, Jin Buhuan's, disciple.
I'm sorry.
I tried my best to stop him,
but I failed.
Once Mentor decides to do something,
no one can stop him.
Here.
What is this?
This is the hot syrup Grandpa Jin taught us to make.
Grandpa Jin says hot syrup is better than immortal soup.
It's super delicious!
Really?
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Go have fun.
Look at these kids.
Without this orphanage,
they might be begging on the streets today,
and tomorrow they might be targeting someone's purse.
When they grow up,
will they think that in life
there are only two paths: deceive or be deceived?
I helped Mentor set up this orphanage
hoping to
give these children a chance
a chance to choose a different life.
In the past, your mentor taught you to strike fast and con slow.
Now that these kids have you,
they won't need to learn those things.
The right path is always hard to walk.
But I'll keep going.
How did it go?
The information the girls collected
will be ready soon.
Almost 4 boxes of them.
I've prepared the boat tickets
to send them away.
You must
protect them for me.
Don't worry.
I will take good care of them.
I've been preparing for this day for a long time.
This time,
it will succeed.
[Richards Grand Hotel]
Chairman Liu gracing us tonight
is my, Siyuan's, greatest honor.
Little Feng,
you handle things very well.
Right now,
Yucheng needs talents like you.
I will have to rely heavily on you in the future, Chairman Liu.
Congratulations, Director Feng.
You're about to be promoted.
With Chairman Liu's connection,
your future career
will surely skyrocket.
Whether it skyrockets
still depends on the Yin Book.
I have only one goal:
to eradicate the Tianxiang Sect.
Sect Master is very cautious.
He won't hide the Yin Book in Tianxiang Sect.
Go to the Yuzhong River,
under the riverbank of the third stone bridge upstream,
find a hidden post,
and you'll be able to get the Yin Book.
Don't move!
Get out!
Yes.
Feng Siyuan.
Your time is coming.
Zhang Dancheng is dead.
He stabbed himself to death
just to trade for your life.
But I don't understand.
Why did you come back
instead of running away?
Later, I figured it out.
Feng Siyuan—
he came looking for me time and again.
I guessed that
you must be hiding behind him.
Do you think I would be so stupid
as to let him raid my sect?
Don't worry.
Everyone has cleared out long ago.
You're pretty good at pretending to be my son.
Drop the act.
It's just the two of us here now.
Haven't you always wanted to kill me?
Come on.
I'll grant your wish.
What?
Can't bring yourself to do it?
I know
in your eyes, I'm a bad person.
Then who is a good person?
Old Sect Master?
Was he a good person?
Back then,
he used the slogan of overthrowing Qing and restoring Ming
to make hundreds of brothers starve
while scamming and dying for him.
In the end, many ended up dead or injured.
He was a bad guy!
And me?
I made sure the brothers ate well,
wore decent clothes,
and looked like respectable men on the streets.
When others see them,
they even have to greet them with a smile.
It was me!
Who gave them dignity!
You gave them dignity?
You clearly made them live worse than pigs and dogs.
You're still too green.
Sometimes I think
you are a bit like me when I was young.
You should understand me.
Now it seems
you're still too young.
That's why you've ended up on a dead end.
I'm not the one who's at a dead end,
it's you.
Yes.
Of course you want me to be at a dead end.
So you turned to Feng Siyuan.
Let me tell you
what kind of person he is.
When he was a head soldier,
he survived by pretending to be dead.
Now you're telling him
I have some Yin Book.
With it, he can become successfull.
You knew he would ask me for it.
If I can't give it to him,
I'll die.
Is that what you think?
But what you don't know is
I really have this Yin Book.
And I will cooperate very well
with Feng Siyuan.
What about you?
In his eyes,
you're just an abandoned pawn.
You're useless.
So I advise you
to just go die.
Die far away, don't dirty my turf.
Thanks to you,
Yanzi and Silly Liang
die a quick death too.
Speak of the devil.
Director Feng.
You were tricked by him.
This Yin Book
really exists.
But it's in my brain— you can't take it away.
But whatever you want to know or ask,
just ask.
I will definitely tell you.
As the saying goes,
relying on oneself is better than relying on others.
What is this?
Sect Master.
Why can't you recognize the Yin Book
in front of Director Feng?
With this set of Yin Book,
I shan't keep the one
in your mind.
You conjured something out of nothing.
Don't worry.
Your retribution
is not over yet.
Good job.
I'll go with you.
Your blood debt
must be paid with your blood.
These are people who have lost their families
because of Tianxiang Sect.
They are here today
to send you off.
How does it feel?
It hurts
so darn much.
They hurt more than you.
Father!
Daughter!
Stepmother.
Jialiang!
Jiashu!
You caused all of it.
The Tianxiang Sect
won't let you get away with this!
There's no Tianxiang Sect anymore.
Don't you know how to tell fortune?
Have a go at how long more you can live.
Buy me a bowl
of wontons.
I am here today
to both expose
and atone.
Tianxiang Sect
used to rob the rich and help the poor.
But today,
it's downright filthy.
Extra! Extra!
The biggest fraud organization in Yucheng has been cracked down!
The Tianxiang Sect uses divination to kill and scam people out of their money!
What are you doing?
Execute!
Raise your gun.
Good!
Great!
This Liang, seriously.
He ran away
without saying goodbye.
He said if we said goodbye in person,
his wheels might not work anymore.
What does he plan
to do in the future?
He told me
the happiest thing he did in Tianxiang Sect
is cracking down
on Plum Blossom Sect,
saving so many children.
He plans to
travel around
to teach scammers a lesson.
What about you?
What's your plan for the future?
I'll think about it after leaving Yucheng.
Being further away
makes some things
become lighter.
You're right.
The past
is too heavy.
It's time to let it go.
People
should look forward.
We're going to say goodbye.
Give me a gift.
Sure.
What do you want?
I want to know your birthday.
It's today.
What a coincidence.
I never thought
birthday
is something to be happy about.
But from now on,
I can finally
live for myself.
Thank you.
I hope
every minute and every second
from now on belongs to you,
and that you're happy every day.
♪ Under the old city wall ♪
♪ The rain fell gently that year ♪
♪ You walked by with an umbrella, saying loneliness didn't scare you ♪
Happy birthday.
♪ In the future, the blades ♪
From now on,
every minute and every second
♪ Are all hidden in smiles ♪
all belong to us.
♪ An impulsive, spiteful remark cut deep into my heart ♪
♪ You fully know ♪
♪ How weak I am ♪
♪ Yet you always turn around, shielding me from harsh words and cold daggers ♪
♪ May you journey toward your future ♪
♪ Leave this stormy sea behind ♪
♪ Let the toxic love we shared ♪
♪ Be the moss that helps you grow ♪
♪ May you find your way out of the haze that is us ♪
♪ Leave me out of your story ♪
♪ Should freedom be your ultimate desire ♪
♪ I shall bloom for you in silence ♪
[Six months later]
Jiaxian,
a letter for you.
Thanks.
Bye.
[To Wang Jiaxian]
Jiaxian,
how have you been?
I now have a disciple,
and I had him to write this letter for you.
In Yucheng,
I felt suffocated in my chest.
I've been able to breathe well since I came out.
The Chrysler you gave me—
it's truly a gas guzzler.
I can't drive it that much.
If you have time, shall we meet?
Bring Feiyan too.
The three of us
and try doing something together again.
I hope all is well with you
and things are peaceful.
Missing you, Liang.
Wang Jiaxian.
Sir,
you know me?
My name is...
Shangguan Chengming.